# MAHMOUD MUHAMMAD ZAKI

**Q** Cairo, Egypt **Z**zmm2343@gmail.com **□** 01068780771

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced Accountant with 1 years of working in a corporate environment. In-depth knowledge of financial processes, budgeting, and accounting principles. Skilled in customer service, problem solving, and providing timely solutions. Applying for the position of Guest Specialist to ensure customer satisfaction and retention.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Sales**

Clothes store

April 2020 - Present, Elmokattam-Cairo

· Meeting Customers, Helping them to find what they need, and is responsible for selling products.

# **Agent**

We

May 2019 - January 2020, Cairo

•technical support to clients in person and remotely. Giving such assistance means that it's all about solving problems from the moment they call the customer service line until the caller's issues are resolved.

## **Agent**

Xceed

July 2018 - March 2019, Cairo

· Generated new business opportunities through cold-calling, email campaigns, sales outreach initiatives, and nurturing key relationships

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Commerce**

Minor in no · Ain shams University · Abbasia Square · 2022 · 3.00

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **PFA**

Ain Shams university · 2022

# Diploma in electronic Accounting programs

IAT Academy · 2022

# Diploma in professional comprehensive accountant

IAT Academy · 2022

#### Trainee

Bank Masr · 2022

### **Trainee**

Marwa Ahmed Othman Accountant Office • 2022

### **SKILLS**

#### Sales

**Customer service** 

**Computer skills** 

Team building

**Communication skills** 

**Emotional intelligence**